BIOGRAPHY

I'm 23 years old Film and Video Editor in Chennai. I have five years of work experience in various positions and worked in Feature Films, Short films, Corporate films and advertisement, Wedding films, Music videos, Fashion promos, Channel promos and Serials.

EXPERIENCE

TRUE DREAMS, COIMBATORE

Photography & Postproduction Studio Video Editor - July 2014- DEC 2014

THE FOTO, COIMBATORE

Photography & Postproduction Studio Video Editor - Aug 2015-July 2016

FIFTHANGLE STUDIOS, CHENNAI

Photography & Postproduction Studio Video Editor - JUN 2017-JAN 2018

SUPER TV, DELHI

Playout & Communication Department
Playout Technician - DEC 2014-JUN 2015

ZERO GRAVITY, CHENNAI

Photography & Postproduction Studio Video Editor - July 2016-Jun 2017

FOCUSING ZONE, CHENNAI

Photography & Postproduction Studio Video Editor - FEB 2018-JUN 2018

FEATURE FILMS

ASSISTANT FILM EDITOR (2018-2019)

Am Assist Under **Bhuvan Srinivasan** an Indian film editor, who works in the Tamil film industry. Under his Projects am worked in **Kalidas(2019), Pathinettampadi(2019), Godfather(2020), Thamizharasan(2020)**.

BHUVAN SRINIVASAN (FILM EDITOR)

He is an Indian film editor, worked as an associate editor to Sreekar Prasad. He mainly involved in the projects such as Raavanan (2010), Agent Vinod (2012), Cocktail (2012), Thuppakki (2012) and Kadal (2013). He has moved on to work on the movies Demonte Colony (2015), Kanithan (2016), Iru Mugan (2016), Kuttram 23 (2016) and Imaikkaa Nodigal (2018).

KALIDAS(2019) (TAMIL)

Kaalidas is a action crime thriller film directed by **Sri Senthil**. The film features **Bharath** and **Ann Sheetal** in the lead roles.

PATHINETTAM PADI(2019) (MALAYALAM)

Pathinettam Padi directed by **Shankar Ramakrishnan**. The film features Ahaana Krishna, Akshay Radhakrishnan, Ashwin and **Mammootty, Prithviraj**, **Arya** in extended cameo roles.

GOD FATHER (2020) (TAMIL)

Godfather is a Indian thriller film directed by **Jagan**. The film features **NATRAJ(Natty)** and **Annanya**, **Lal** in the lead roles.

THAMIZHARASAN (2020) (TAMIL)

Thamilarasan is an action film directed by Babu Yogeswaran.Starring Vijay Antony, Ramya Nambeesan,Suresh Gopi and music scored by Ilaiyaraaja.

EDUCATION

GHSS,COIMBATORE

SSLC-2011

GOVT POLYTECHNIC.COIMBATORE

DIPLOMA IN CIVIL-2011-2014

LANGUAGES

TAMIL

READ AND WRITE

ENGLISH

READ AND WRITE

SKILLS

Premier Pro

After Effects

Final Cut Pro

AVID

Davince Ressolve

